目前，这是我们的天气预报列表. 它看着还可以，
Currently, this is our forecast list. It looks okay, but
但是要是我们能把温度符号加上那就更好了
it would be nice if we could show the degree
最佳实践就是使用这个标注。
symbol for these temperature values. Using this notation is best
它可以帮助翻译器了解如何重排文本和参数
practice. It will help the translator know how to reorder the
来符合本地语言习惯。
text and the parameters so that it fits the local
那么接下来我们看一下如何用这个办法
language. Now let's look at how we can use this
在我们的应用中格式化温度数据。在string.xml文件中
method to format temperatures within our app. Within the string.xml
我们声明了温度字符资源。我们使用xliff标签
file, we declared the format temperature string resource. We use xliff
来指明这是十进制温度数据的位置，
tag to denote that this is where the decimal temperature
后面紧跟着温度符号的Unicode值
value will go. This is followed by the unicode
在Utility类中，
character for the degrees symbol. In the utility class, in
我们可以在formatTemperature方法中使用该字符串资源。
the format temperature method, we can use this string resource. Remember
记住，在这个方法中，我们需要传递两个参数：温度值
that, in this method, we take in a temperature and
和用户是使用公制单位还是英制单位的选项。
a user's preference for metric or imperial. Then, we return
之后该方法会返回已转换的温度值。之后我们还会修改这个方法
the converted temperature. We're going to modify this method so that
使它能返回一个带有温度符号的字符串。
it also returns the formatted string with a degrees symbol after
要实现这个，在传递参数的时候我们还要传递一个context引用
the value. In order to do this. We need to pass
通过context，我们可以获得之前所声明的字符串的ID
a context. From the context we can get access to the
然后我们还可以将其他附加的参数
string resource ID that we declared earlier. Then we passed in any
传递给字符模板。而在这个例子中
additional parameters for that string template. In this case we only have
仅需要传递一个温度值即可。
one parameters so we pass in the temperature value. Then this
然后该方法会返回一个温度格式的字符串。
fully formatted string gets returned to the caller. This method is used
这个方法被用在天气预报列表里，同时也用在详细内容页面。
in the forecast list, as well in the detail page. So we
所以我们也要在那里更新相关代码，这样他就会以新的参数编译。
also had to update the code there so that it would compile
这就是程序修改后的样子。
with this new parameter. And this is what the app looks like fter
那么动手在你的代码里使用字符资源
the change. Go ahead and make the change in your code to add a
显示温度吧！
string resource for displaying temperature in
完成后在方框里打钩。
degrees. Check this box when you're done.
请记住用这个语句格式来实现
And remember, use this notation going forward
字符串的格式化操作。
for when you need to format strings